I woke up to one of my exes being named alongside Harvey Weinstein in the Epstein file.
So I'm on one today.
The reason these are unprecedented times is because you know better.
That's what makes them unprecedented times.
We have always had, in the last memory of written record, terrible people.
The difference is that now you know.
White people, you know how terrible the folks have been to uphold whiteness.
You know.
The unprecedented time is not that there's a new level of devil.
The unprecedented time is that the people now understand the level of devil.
That's what makes the time unprecedented.
Don't ask me dumb questions like, what's your views on Kamala Harris?
I consider you a bot and an op.
Where the fuck is Kamala Harris even to be viewed?
Because last I checked, she went and did a book deal and then went and sat down.
And there's going to be a black person who says, well, you know, black people don't need to be in the front line.
She needs to be sitting down.
First and foremost, she told y'all, I will never make a law just for black people because I have to make sure that everybody is positively affected by that law.
So therefore, by her own philosophy, she should be out there for everybody affected by the laws.
So there's that.
Again, this is actually a great segue to Democrats.
If you're still calling yourself a Democrat, you are literally the problem.
If you are still believing that there is any level of recompense to be had for Democrats, you are an op.
So all of you all who thought if I just vote for Kamala Harris and don't make any demands that she behave differently than the party that she is a part of, then we will be all right.
You were an op and you tried to call me an op.
And those of us who said, hey, she needs to show up different.
At this point, if you are showing up to the table and you're not carrying an ax, I don't care that you're there.
I'm going to say that again for all of you all who love to run this whole, well, we got to get a seat at the table.
If you're at the table and you do not have an ax, I don't care if you're there because you are not in the effort of dismantling that which harms us.
And so many of you think that harm reduction is a real thing and all it is is privilege perseverance.
That's it. Miss me with all that nonsense of harm reduction because the same people continue to be harmed.
The people at the bottom. And why are they at the bottom?
Because the people that you are continuing to preserve and protect and vote for always make sure that there is a bottom.
They always ensure that there is a bottom.
There shouldn't need to be a bottom.
Hold on, let me block this person.
So when I see these people still talking about Democrats, confounded.
Oh my God.
Someone in here is really talking about, I think Kamala is planning her next plan.
Kamala.
Why do y'all think Kamala is smart?
This is not even about Kamala Harris.
This is a greater question.
Why do you think Kamala Harris is smart?
What has she demonstrated that makes you think that she's smart?
Why do you think Barack Obama was smart?
Why do you think Joseph Biden was smart?
Why do you think any of these people are smart?
What is it about them that makes you think that they are smart, that they are somewhere planning?
What is it about these people in these positions that makes you think they have the wherewithal to strategize?
Miss F. Reid, I made you the moderator.
Because so often, I see people assigning a level of capability to these people for no reason.
And I wonder, have you fallen prey to the lie that because they're in a suit, that because they're on TV, that they are somehow smarter than you?
Because they have quite often undermined those who actually are smart so that they can stay in power.
Someone said she was the 32nd District Attorney of California.
What does that have to do with intellect?
I just want to understand.
Why do you think that someone being elected makes them smart?
They smart enough to get the check and the reputation, and that's about it.
That's not smart.
That's savvy.
And for what it's worth, at this point, passing an exam is not an indicator of your intellect.
Because as we have seen, folks can absolutely fake passing an exam.
We saw all these rich white kids get into rich-ass and prestigious schools with fake scores.
So you having an exam score does not by any means make me say you're intelligent.
Because I can tell you, you know who does terrible on exams?
Me.
A bona fide smart person.
Terrible.
I got a fucking 10-13 on my SAT.
The second time I took it, after doing a whole SAT prep class, I got a 10-30.
No, I got an 11-30.
I went up.
Ooh.
These exams were literally created, by the way, because of racism.
So don't tell me that someone passed an exam and that makes them smart.
Because the reality is that being able to memorize does not, in essence, mean that you are smart.
It means you're able to memorize.
Which, don't get me wrong, is an aspect of intellect.
Retention.
However, being able to retain and spit it out doesn't make you smart.
Doesn't mean you're smart.
When we're looking at the Democrats, we're looking at duplicitousness.
We're looking at nefariousness.
We're looking at people who have partnered with other people to manipulate you.
To persuade you to doubt what you know is true.
They literally used, shout out to Crutches and Spice for pointing this out.
They literally used a story from 2023 and presented it as if it happened now, under the auspices of it being the result of Donald Trump's policies, when it happened under the presidency of Joseph Robinette Guyton.
Where it's unprecedented because now we are aware.
And when people say, what do we do?
Do something fucking different.
How about that?
Do something different.
Question.
Because in every other facet of your life, you would be able to apply a basic sense of common sense.
Oh, when I drove in that direction, there was traffic.
So tomorrow, I'm going to take a different route so that there will be less traffic.
Throw up.
So I'm not going to eat that food again.
I ate bad curry goat in 1995 and I ain't never ate curry goat again.
Learn my lesson.
You identify, hey, we keep these people.
We keep donating these people.
We keep elevating these people.
We keep believing in these people and they keep doing nothing.
Maybe you should start with stopping donating, stopping elevating, stopping believing in, and stopping identifying yourself as one of those people.
Start there.
It is unprecedented times because now you know.
We can no longer pretend that we are ignorant.
That is what makes it unprecedented times.
We were brought into a world that we didn't understand.
And now we do.
And so once you are able to see that, you have to then start doing the work from the inside out.
Actively trying to ruin the earth with a classification of race that has been using me to ruin the world.
You see what I'm saying?
And then someone here says, but after this, what does life look like after?
What is the point?
Question.
Imagine what it can look like after.
How about you do that?
Don't tell me, don't ask me what does it look like after.
You have the capability to imagine something better.
Tell me what it looks like after.
Actually processes together in unison.
Then we can identify together how to bring that to reality.
You know what's another reality a lot of people don't want to admit?
The cool table is always PDFs and ARPists.
That is the cool table.
Because when you live in a world where the folks who run it are PDFs and ARPists,
then you know that anyone who is trying to get to that place of power
is going to have to either become a PDF or an ARPist,
or they're going to allow it.
And what we have to be able to acknowledge,
and this is me literally just assuming that the people on here in my live
are not terrible people.
We have to acknowledge that anyone we know
who is attempting to ascend is willing.
We have to know that anyone who has achieved the level of ascension
has either participated or turned the other head,
turned the other cheek.
This is what I mean by unprecedented times.
Getting real, real.
Yes, Sabs, join my Patreon.
It's $5.
That's what unprecedented times means.
So, when people are saying,
well, we don't know, and we're not sure, and we're not careful,
you have to know what you're about.
And you have to be ready to take on whatever turning the other cheek is going to cause you.
That is a stupid suggestion.
You should run for the presidency.
For what it's worth, I think anybody running for electoral office right now is wildin'.
I don't endorse candidates anyway.
But again, anybody running for electoral office right now, I'm looking at you like, what are you doing?
Why are we donating to people running for electoral office?
So you could join in the fuckery?
You're not going to change it.
Are you going to even be able to get on the ballot if you're an actual agent for change?
You cannot change any of this from being a part of it.
Yes, even join.
What?
You step into the fuckery, I'm going to change it.
No, you're not.
You're not going to change it.
And it's wild to think that you're going to because you then, what that means is you have not seen the size of the system.
Anytime you enter it, you are upholding it.
Those are my three points today.
One, the Dems are trash.
They've been trash.
If you're not actively telling folks about the Dems being trash, I don't know what you're doing.
Two, the folks who want to be on top are always going to be PDFs and ARPists.
That's just what it is.
Because right now in the world that we live in, the folks at the top are all PDFs and ARPists.
And they consider that to be a necessity.
You have to be willing to do that to get in.
That's why there's an entire file.
Everybody who is still in support of Israel is supporting PDFs and ARPists.
Israel is a safe haven for PDFs and ARPists.
That is representational of the system that controls the world because Israel is their baby.
So, if we do not collectively begin with inwardly saying, I will not allow it, the unacceptable cannot be accepted.
If we don't start doing that with ourselves first, then we cannot expect it to change ever.
These are unprecedented times because we know.
They are unprecedented times because we are able to see it and to turn and shift and undermine it.
That is why they are unprecedented times.
So, it behooves you to get unprecedented in how you live.
Whatever way you've been living up until this point needs to change.
You need to expand.
You need to find a greater concept of your capabilities.
And that's going to happen from actualizing your thoughts into reality.
Follow me on Patreon.
I'm now on upscrolled.
Buy my book at AmandaLandExports.
I have a new drop coming out tomorrow called How Black Am I Gonna Have to Get.
Mwah.
Stay lifted.